tinymce.com 2019-12-23

# Privacy Policy - Your Privacy Rights - Tiny

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY.   **BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  YOU SHOULD CHECK THIS POLICY REGULARLY TO SEE IF ANY CHANGES HAVE BEEN MADE.

Your privacy is important. Tiny Technologies Inc. has created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our websites or use our products, why we collect it, how it is used, and how it is stored. This Privacy Policy explains the data collection and use practices of Tiny Technologies Inc. with our Services. The terms “you,” “your,” “yours,” and “user” refer to the customer, purchaser, user or visitor utilizing our Services. The terms “Company,” “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Tiny Technologies Inc.

By using the Site, you consent to the data collection and use practices prescribed in this Privacy Policy.  We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit our websites to review our Privacy Policy.

## 1\. Definitions

“ **Tiny** ” means Ephox Corporation DBA Tiny Technologies Inc. and all of its subsidiary companies.

“ **Personal Data** ” means any information that can be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number or other contact information, whether at work or at home, as defined in Article 4 of the EU General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR).

“ **Privacy Policy”** means this policy effective as of: July 16, 2018.

“ **Service** ” or “ **Services** ” means any product or service that Tiny provides or offers and include your interaction with our websites and any information we may collect from your use of our websites.

## 2\. What information we collect

We collect information about you when you provide it to us, when you use our Services, and when other sources provide it to us, as further described below.

### **2.1 Information you give to us**

We collect information about you when you input it into the Services or otherwise provide it directly to us.

**Account and Profile Information** : We collect information about you when you register for an account, create or modify your profile, set preferences, sign-up for or make purchases through the Services. For example, you provide your contact information and, in some cases, billing information when you register for the Services. You also have the option of adding a display name, job title, and other details to your profile information to be displayed in our Services. We keep track of your preferences when you select settings within the Services.

**Content you provide through our products** : The Services include the Tiny products you use, where we collect and store content that you post, send, receive and share. This content includes any information about you that you may choose to include. Content also includes the files and links you upload to the Services.

**Content you provide through our websites** : The Services also include our websites owned or operated by us. We collect other content that you submit to these websites, which include social media or social networking websites operated by us. For example, you provide content to us when you provide feedback or when you participate in any interactive features, surveys, contests, promotions, sweepstakes, activities or events.

**Information you provide through our support channels** : The Services also include our customer support, where you may choose to submit information regarding a problem you are experiencing with a Service. Whether you designate yourself as a technical contact, open a support ticket, speak to one of our representatives directly or otherwise engage with our support team, you will be asked to provide contact information, a summary of the problem you are experiencing, and any other documentation, screenshots or information that would be helpful in resolving the issue.

**Payment Information** : We collect certain payment and billing information when you register for certain paid Services. For example, we ask you to designate a billing representative, including name and contact information, upon registration. You might also provide payment information, such as payment card details, which we collect via secure payment processing services.

**Job Applications** : When you are applying for a job with us we will collect Personal Data from you that relates to you and the job you are applying for.

### **2.2       Information we collect automatically when you use the Services**

We collect information about you when you use our Services, including browsing our websites and taking certain actions within the Services.

**Your use of the Services** : We keep track of certain information about you when you visit and interact with any of our Services. This information includes the features you use; the links you click on; the type, size and filenames of attachments you upload to the Services; frequently used search terms; and how you interact with others on the Services.

**Device and Connection Information** : We collect information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other devices you use to access the Services. This device information includes your connection type and settings when you install, access, update, or use our Services. We also collect information through your device about your operating system, browser type, IP address, URLs of referring/exit pages, device identifiers, and crash data. We use your IP address and/or country preference in order to approximate your location to provide you with a better Service experience. How much of this information we collect depends on the type and settings of the device you use to access the Services.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies** : Tiny and our third-party partners, such as our advertising and analytics partners, use cookies and other tracking technologies (e.g., web beacons, device identifiers and pixels) to provide functionality and to recognize you across different Services and devices. For more information, please see our Cookies and Tracking Notice.

### **2.3       Information we receive from other sources**

We receive information about you from other Service users, from third-party services, from our related companies, and from our business and channel partners.

**Other users of the Services** : Other users of our Services may provide information about you when they submit content through the Services. For example, you may be mentioned in technical support issue opened by someone else. We also receive your email address from other Service users when they provide it in order to invite you to the Services.

**Tiny Companies** : We receive information about you from companies that are owned or operated by Tiny, in accordance with their terms and policies.

**Tiny Partners** : We work with a global network of partners who provide consulting, implementation, training and other services around our products. Some of these partners also help us to market and promote our products, generate leads for us, and resell our products. We receive information from these partners, such as billing information, billing and technical contact information, company name, what Tiny products you have purchased or may be interested in, evaluation information you have provided, what events you have attended, and what country you are in.

**Other Partners** : We receive information about you and your activities on and off the Services from third-party partners, such as advertising and market research partners who provide us with information about your interest in and engagement with, our Services and online advertisements.

## **3\. How we use information we collect**

How we use the information we collect depends in part on which Services you use, how you use them, and any preferences you have communicated to us. Below are the specific purposes for which we use the information we collect about you.

**To provide the Services and personalize your experience** : We use information about you to provide the Services to you, including to process transactions with you, authenticate you when you log in, provide customer support, and operate and maintain the Services.

**To communicate with you about the Services** : We use your contact information to send transactional communications via email and within the Services, including confirming your purchases, reminding you of subscription expirations, responding to your comments, questions and requests, providing customer support, and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and administrative messages.

**To market, promote and drive engagement with the Services** : We use your contact information and information about how you use the Services to send promotional communications that may be of special interest to you, including by email and by displaying Tiny ads on other companies’ websites and applications, as well as on platforms like Facebook and Google. These communications are aimed at driving engagement and maximizing what you get out of the Services, including information about new features, survey requests, newsletters, and events we think may be of interest to you. We also communicate with you about new product offers, promotions and contests. You can control whether you receive these communications as described below under “Optout of communications.”

**Customer support** : We use your information to resolve technical issues you encounter, to respond to your requests for assistance, to analyze crash information, and to repair and improve the Services.

**For safety and security** : We use information about you and your Service use to verify accounts and activity, to monitor suspicious or fraudulent activity and to identify violations of Service policies.

**To protect our legitimate business interests and legal rights** : Where required by law or where we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights, interests and the interests of others, we use information about you in connection with legal claims, compliance, regulatory, and audit functions, and disclosures in connection with the acquisition, merger or sale of a business.

**With your consent** : We use information about you where you have given us consent to do so for a specific purpose not listed above. For example, we may publish testimonials or featured customer stories to promote the Services, with your permission.

## 4\. Legal bases for processing (for EU users)

If you are an individual in the European Union (“EU”), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws. The legal bases depend on the Services you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only where:

  1. We need it to provide you the Services, including to operate the Services, provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the Services;
  2. It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Services and to protect our legal rights and interests;
  3. You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or
  4. We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place. Where we are using your information because we or a third party (e.g. your employer) have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services.

## 5\. How we share information we collect

We share information about you through the Services and with certain third parties. We share information we collect about you in the ways discussed below, including in connection with possible business transfers, but we are not in the business of selling information about you to advertisers or other third parties.

### **5.1     Sharing with other service users**

When you use the Services, we share certain information about you with other Service users.

**Community Forums** : Our websites offer publicly accessible blogs, forums, issue trackers, and wikis like Tiny Community and Tiny Developer Community. You should be aware that any information you provide on these websites – including profile information associated with the account you use to post the information – may be read, collected, and used by any member of the public who accesses these websites. Your posts and certain profile information may remain even after you terminate your account. We urge you to consider the sensitivity of any information you input into these Services. To request removal of your information from publicly accessible websites operated by us, please contact us as provided below. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to and why.

### **5.2     Sharing with third parties**

We share information with third parties that help us operate, provide, improve, integrate, customize, support and market our Services.

**Service Providers** : We work with third-party service providers to provide website and application development, hosting, maintenance, backup, storage, virtual infrastructure, payment processing, analysis and other services for us, which may require them to access or use information about you. If a service provider needs to access information about you to perform services on our behalf, they do so under close instruction from us, including policies and procedures designed to protect your information.

Tiny’s third-party service providers are:

  * Amazon Web Services [data processing infrastructure]
  * Braintree [payment processing]
  * Datapine [Cloud services analytics]
  * Dovetail [website analytics]
  * Eventbrite [event ticketing]
  * Facebook [advertising, social media marketing]
  * FullContact, Inc. [email marketing]
  * Google Inc [website analytics]
  * Informizely [surveys]
  * Jazz [HR, hiring]
  * LinkedIn [advertising, social media marketing]
  * Mailchimp [email marketing]
  * Metorik [WooCommerce data analysis]
  * NetSuite [accounting]
  * Olark [online chat]
  * PayPal [payment processing]
  * Recurly [payment & subscription processing]
  * Salesforce [customer relationship management]
  * Salesforce (Community) [online community management, forum]
  * Salesforce (Pardot) [email marketing]
  * Survey Monkey [surveys]
  * Twitter [advertising, social media marketing]
  * Wootric [surveys]
  * WPEngine [hosting services]
  * Zendesk [support]

**Tiny Partners** : We work with third parties who provide consulting, sales, and technical services to deliver and implement customer solutions around the Services. We may share your information with these third parties in connection with their services, such as to assist with billing and collections, to provide localized support, and to provide customizations. We may also share information with these third parties where you have agreed to that sharing.

**With your consent** : We share information about you with third parties when you give us consent to do so. For example, we often display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our public websites. With your consent, we may post your name alongside the testimonial.

**Compliance with Enforcement Requests and Applicable Laws** ; Enforcement of Our Rights: In exceptional circumstances, we may share information about you with a third party if we believe that sharing is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, including to meet national security requirements, (b) enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) protect the security or integrity of our products and services, (d) protect Tiny, our customers or the public from harm or illegal activities, or (e) respond to an emergency which we believe in good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person.

**Business Transfers:** We may share or transfer information we collect under this privacy policy in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Services if a transaction takes place, as well as any choices you may have regarding your information.

## 6\. How we store and secure information we collect

**Information storage and security**

We use data hosting service providers in the United States to host the information we collect, and we use technical measures to secure your data.

While we implement safeguards designed to protect your information, no security system is impenetrable and due to the inherent nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that data, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, is absolutely safe from intrusion by others.

If you use our server or data center Services, responsibility for access to the information you put into the Services rests with you and not Tiny.

**How long we keep information**

How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, as described in further detail below. After such time, we will either delete or anonymize your information or, if this is not possible (for example, because the information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.

**Account information** : We retain your account information for as long as your account is active and a reasonable period thereafter in case you decide to re-activate the Services. We also retain some of your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements, to support business operations, and to continue to develop and improve our Services. Where we retain information for Service improvement and development, we take steps to eliminate information that directly identifies you, and we only use the information to uncover collective insights about the use of our Services, not to specifically analyze personal characteristics about you.

**Information you share on the Services** : If your account is deactivated or disabled, some of your information and the content you have provided will remain in order to allow your team members or other users to make full use of the Services. For example, we continue to display messages you sent to the users that received them and continue to display content you provided.

**Marketing information** : If you have elected to receive marketing emails from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our Services, such as when you last opened an email from us or ceased using your Tiny account. We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created.

## 7\. Cookies and tracking notice

Like many web sites, we also use standard technologies such as “cookies,” which are files placed on your computer’s hard drive by the sites you visit.  Cookies are small text files stored by your browser in your computer when you visit our Site. Websites use temporary cookies called “session” cookies to ensure that you are recognized when you move from page to page within one site and that any information you have entered is remembered. Websites also use cookies called “persistent” cookies to enable a website to remember you on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of services or functions offered. We may install both persistent and session cookies when you visit our Site. We use cookies to improve our Site and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. Most browsers will accept cookies until browser settings are changed to refuse them. If you block or refuse to accept cookies, or delete cookies after visiting our Site, you may not be able to access or use certain features or functions of our Site.

## 8\. Your rights

### **8.1  Your rights in your country**

Your rights will be determined by the country in which you reside. Many counties have specific laws relating to privacy. Tiny seeks to abide with all relevant national laws.

If you reside in the European Union, you have the right under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) to request from Tiny access to and erasure of your Personal Data. If you reside outside of the European Union, you may have similar rights under your local laws.

If you have signed up for an account with us on the Site, you can access or change your Personal Data by logging into your account and editing your profile at our Account Center. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and account information at all times. You may request deletion of your Personal Data at our Account Center or by email at: [legal@tiny.cloud](mailto:legal@tiny.cloud).

If you do not have an account with us accessible on the Site, you can access, change or to request deletion of your Personal Data by emailing us at [legal@tiny.cloud](mailto:legal@tiny.cloud).

We may retain original and updated information for reasons such as, for example: audit, dispute resolution, troubleshooting, and record retention.  For security purposes, we may request information to help verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your information.

### **8.2     Your rights in California**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (“Code”) permits users of our Site who are California residents and have provided Personal Data to us to request from us certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

As required by the Code, at your request we will provide you with the categories of Personal Data that we collect through the Site and the categories of third party persons or entities with whom such Personal Data may be shared. California law requires us to inform you, at your request, of (a) the categories of Personal Data we collect and the third parties with whom we share that information; (b) the names and addresses of those third parties; and (c) examples of the products marketed by those third parties. To make such a request, please send an email to [legal@tiny.cloud](mailto:legal@tiny.cloud) or write us at: Tiny Technologies, Inc. 2100 Geng Rd, Suite 220, Palo Alto, CA 94303-3354, United States of America.

The Code allows you to control the parties with whom we share Personal Data and the specific Personal Data that you do not wish to be shared with those parties. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personal Data you do not want us to share with third parties. The request should be emailed to the attention of our Legal Department, [legal@tiny.cloud](mailto:legal@tiny.cloud) and labeled “California Customer Choice Notice.” We will respond as soon as are able. Please note that there is no charge for processing this request.

## 9\. The Security of your information

To help protect the privacy of the Personal Data you transmit through use of the Services, we use commercially reasonable security practices that are technically feasible for us to protect the user data we collect against unauthorized access, including, without limitation, physical, technical, and administrative safeguards. Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, we use commercially reasonable efforts to limit access to your Personal Data to our employees, agents, and officers who need the information to perform their responsibilities. However, please be aware that the Site and our services are run on software, hardware and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security beyond our control.  We cannot guarantee the security of the information on and sent from our Site, and we are not responsible for the acts and omissions of third parties who receive the information. Please be aware that despite best intentions and the guidelines outlined in this Privacy Policy, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

## 10\. International transfers

Personal Data collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Company or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

You agree to comply with all local laws, rules and regulations regarding online conduct and acceptable content.  Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you agree to comply with all applicable laws, rules and regulations regarding the transmission of data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.

## 11\. Children

Our Services are not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 13.  Any person who provides their information to Company through a Service represents to Tiny that they are 13 years of age or older.

## 12\. Your consent to this privacy policy and updates.

By using the Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy.  This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version.

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy.  When we do, we will indicate the date that this Privacy Policy was last updated.  Any changes we make will be effective immediately upon notice, which we may provide by means including, without limitation, posting a prominent notice on the Site or sending an email to the address associated with your account. We are not responsible for your failure to receive an email due to the actions of your internet service provider or any email filtering service. Consequently, you should add tiny.cloud to the list of domains approved to send you email. Your continued use of the Site after such notice will be deemed acceptance of such changes. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so be sure to return to this page periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of this Privacy Policy.  If we make changes to this Privacy Policy and you continue to use our Site, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy and any updates. We will only use Personal Data in accordance with the Privacy Policy that was in effect at the time the information was collected.

## 13\. Contacting Tiny

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [legal@tiny.cloud](mailto:legal@tiny.cloud) or by postal mail to Tiny Technologies Inc., Legal Department,  2100 Geng Rd, Suite 220, Palo Alto, CA 94303-3354, United States of America.

© Tiny Technologies, Inc.  
July 16, 2018
